<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Willamette Valley Bed and Breakfast - Newberg, Oregon</title>
    <link>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Willamette Valley Bed and Breakfast - Newberg, Oregon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 18:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>McMinnville Wine and Food Classic</title>
      <link>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/events/mcminnville-wine-and-food-classic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/events/mcminnville-wine-and-food-classic/</guid>
      <description>A CELEBRATION OF LOCAL WINE &amp;amp; CUISINE LOVED FAR &amp;amp; WIDE
The 27th annual McMinnville Wine &amp;amp; Food Classic, also known as “Sip!” gathers thousands of people from all over the Pacific Northwest together in celebration of Oregon wine and cuisine at Evergreen Aviation &amp;amp; Space Museum…all for the benefit of children. 2020’s event welcomes returning favorites as well as new producers, assembling 70+ of the region’s best wineries as well as a variety of chefs, bakers, breweries, distilleries, artists, artisans, and musicians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Chardonnay Celebration</title>
      <link>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/events/oregon-chardonnay-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/events/oregon-chardonnay-celebration/</guid>
      <description>GRAND TASTING 2020 | EXPLORING CHARDONNAY FROM ANCIENT SOILS
Saturday, February 22, 2020 | 3:00 – 5:30 p.m.
Join us for a walk-around tasting of more than 50 Oregon Chardonnays from our 2020 Featured Wineries. Following our Grand Seminar theme of Born of Flood &amp;amp; Fire: Ancient Soils of Oregon, wines will be organized by soil type. Interact with winemakers in this uniquely formatted tasting and enjoy light Chardonnay-friendly hors d’œuvres, all in the warm atmosphere of The Allison Inn &amp;amp; Spa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Truffle Festival - Yamhill Wine Country</title>
      <link>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/events/oregon-truffle-festival-yamhill-wine-country/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/events/oregon-truffle-festival-yamhill-wine-country/</guid>
      <description> Oregon wine and truffles: sheer bliss! We celebrate this singular pairing and explore the shared terroir of wine and truffles during our Yamhill weekend in the northern Willamette Valley. Taking place February 14-16, 2020, the Yamhill weekend offers an immersive package for a limited number of truffle aficionados, as well as an action-packed schedule of à la carte events, including cooking classes and our annual Fresh Truffle Marketplace.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubbles Fest 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/events/bubbles-fest-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/events/bubbles-fest-2020/</guid>
      <description>Anne Amie Vineyards:
On February 8th &amp;amp; 9th, 2020 from 11am to 4pm, join us at our sixth annual Bubbles Fest sparkling wine festival.
Join us for a single day, or purchase weekend admission and taste wines from all 25 participating producers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinner with Friends at Winderlea Vineyard and Winery</title>
      <link>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/events/dinner-with-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/events/dinner-with-friends/</guid>
      <description>Winderlea Vineyard and Winery dinner with friends, phone 503-554-5900</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nicolas-Jay Winemaker Dinner with Valley Commissary</title>
      <link>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/events/nicolas-jay-winemaker-dinner-with-valley-commissary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/events/nicolas-jay-winemaker-dinner-with-valley-commissary/</guid>
      <description>Nicolas-Jay proprietors Jean-Nicolas Meo and Jay Boberg invite you into their Dundee home for an intimate winemaker dinner with pairings from Nicolas-Jay and Domaine Meo-Camuzet. 971-412-1124</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archery Summit 8th Annual Crab Feast</title>
      <link>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/events/archery-summit-8th-annual-crab-feast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/events/archery-summit-8th-annual-crab-feast/</guid>
      <description>Friday, January 17 &amp;amp; Saturday, January 18, 2020
Ring in the delectable Pacific Northwest shellfish season with our eighth annual Crab Feast. We’ll serve a special lineup of Archery Summit wines—including current releases and library selections—alongside the culinary creativity of Peter Janiak, our gifted executive chef. On full display will be fresh Oregon Dungeness crab, among the region’s most esteemed and true-to-place ingredients.
Diners will enjoy multiple courses set to seamless wine pairings in the warm company of winery staff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cultivating Experience for the Willamette Valley</title>
      <link>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/posts/cultivating-experience-for-the-willamette-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 03:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/posts/cultivating-experience-for-the-willamette-valley/</guid>
      <description>With the newly completed addition of guest suites, our bed and breakfast in Oregon wine country has had me thinking about the career events that have built up to this point. We have actually been preparing for years to be ready to welcome guests into our home, honing our skills in related industries in preparation for one of the biggest events of our lives. I have spent 28+ years in the hotel industry at some of the nicest properties in the west, holding positions throughout several departments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Retreat in Willamette Valley</title>
      <link>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/posts/building-a-retreat-in-willamette-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 23:25:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.willamettevalleybandb.com/posts/building-a-retreat-in-willamette-valley/</guid>
      <description>It has been our dream for years now to open up a Bed &amp;amp; Breakfast, and with our background in hospitality, retail, art and wine we have found an ideal spot here in Newberg, Oregon to make that dream come true. We love being in the heart of the Willamette Valley where we are amongst the vineyards and close to the wineries yet close to town so we can take advantage of all those conveniences as well, and we are currently building five beautiful suites with all the amenities in mind to make you feel right at home when you come to visit!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>